Chase Going Woodhouse Papers 1983.0009
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Writings, undated, 1923-1961
  - Unpublished articles
    - "Institute of Women's Professional Relations.", ca. 1934 (Box 3:, Folder 70)
    - "Jobs on the airlines.", undated (Box 3:, Folder 71)
    - "Marriage and another job.", ca. 1934 (Box 3:, Folder 72)
    - "The married woman teacher.", ca. 1934 (Box 3:, Folder 73)
    - "Married women work.", undated (Box 3:, Folder 74)
    - "Money cost of children in business and professional families.", 1929 (Box 3:, Folder 75)
    - "Occupations requiring a knowledge of art.", undated (Box 3:, Folder 76)
    - "Organized women and the new politics.", undated (Box 3:, Folder 77)
    - "The policewoman.", undated (Box 3:, Folder 78)
    - "Poultry and eggs in Connecticut.", 1950 (Box 3:, Folder 79)
    - "The professional mother.", undated (Box 3:, Folder 80)
    - "The public health statistician.", undated (Box 3:, Folder 81)
    - "The root of all evil.", undated (Box 3:, Folder 82)
    - "Secretarial job in business.", undated (Box 3:, Folder 83)
    - "The standard of living mothers' pension families in the District of Columbia.", ca. 1934 (Box 3:, Folder 84)
    - "The status of the homemanager today.", 1938 (Box 3:, Folder 85)
    - "Status of women in American social life.", undated (Box 4:, Folder 86)
    - "The trained woman over 40.", undated (Box 4:, Folder 87)
    - "Trends in occupations for women with graduate degrees.", undated (Box 4:, Folder 88)
    - "Typography.", undated (Box 4:, Folder 89)
    - "Where to use your mathematics in a job.", undated (Box 4:, Folder 90)
    - "Who employs the artist?", undated (Box 4:, Folder 91)
    - "Who should provide the home income?", undated (Box 4:, Folder 92)
    - "Women in business and the professions, 1910-1930.", ca. 1932 (Box 4:, Folder 93)
    - "Would married women were people.", undated (Box 4:, Folder 94)
    - [Vocational guidance], undated (Box 4:, Folder 95)
    - "The volunteer.", 1961 (Box 4:, Folder 96)
    - "You and your job.", undated (Box 4:, Folder 97)
    - Article fragments, undated (Box 4:, Folder 98)
  - Speeches
    - 1948—American's year of decision (Box 4:, Folder 99)
    - [American Commission on Children and Youth], undated (Box 4:, Folder 100)
    - Are women effective citizens?, undated (Box 4:, Folder 101)
    - Barnard College, 1950 (Box 4:, Folder 102)
    - College women in a reorganizing world [abstract], 1941 (Box 4:, Folder 103)
    - Commencement, undated (Box 4:, Folder 104)
    - Connecticut State Farm Bureau Federation Banquet, ca. 1950 (Box 4:, Folder 105)
    - Critical analyses of values, undated (Box 4:, Folder 106)
    - Education for citizenship through vocational education, 1947 (Box 4:, Folder 107)
    - [Florida Retail Grocers, Fight against inflation], undated (Box 4:, Folder 108)
    - [Girl Scouts Dinner], undated (Box 4:, Folder 109)
    - Hunter College, undated (Box 4:, Folder 110)
    - Jobs for 1938 (Box 4:, Folder 111)
    - Marriage and a profession, 1929 (Box 4:, Folder 112)
    - [Medical Service Vocation], undated (Box 4:, Folder 113)
    - NEPC Panel, undated (Box 4:, Folder 114)
    - Robinson, Florence (Connecticut College), 1938 (Box 4:, Folder 115)
    - Some trends in women's work today, 1936 (Box 4:, Folder 116)
    - State Technical College commencement, 1942 (Box 4:, Folder 117)
    - Temperment and careers, undated (Box 4:, Folder 118)
    - Volunteers, undated (Box 4:, Folder 119)
    - What vocations are open to young people?, 1936 (Box 4:, Folder 120)
    - [Women and the New Deal], ca. 1940 (Box 4:, Folder 121)
    - Speech notes, undated (Box 4:, Folder 122)
    - Speech notes, undated (Box 4:, Folder 123)
    - Speeches not by CGW, undated (Box 4:, Folder 124)
  - Correspondence
    - Requests to contribute articles, 1946-1947 (Box 4:, Folder 125)
  - Abstracts and Notes
    - Abstracts, undated (Box 4:, Folder 126-127)
    - Abstracts, undated (Box 5:, Folder 128-138)
    - Notes, undated (Box 5:, Folder 139-141)
    - Notes, undated (Box 6:, Folder 142-151)
    - Notes [War Manpower Commission], ca. 1934 (Box 6:, Folder 152)
    - Notes [Women in the General Assembly], 1967 (Box 6:, Folder 153)
- Series II: Auerbach Service Bureau, undated, 1944-1981
  - Subseries A: Annual Reports, 1944-1976
    - Annual Report, Reports by Bureau Director, 1944; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:1 (Box 7, Folder 1 [39153019709817])
      Annual Reports; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Annual Report, Reports by Bureau Director, 1945; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:2 (Box 7, Folder 2 [39153019709973])
    - Annual Report, Reports by Bureau Director, 1946; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:3 (Box 7, Folder 3 [39153019709981])
    - Annual Report, 1946-1947; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:4 (Box 7, Folder 4 [39153019709999])
    - Annual Report, 1947-1948; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:5 (Box 7, Folder 5 [39153019710005])
    - Annual Report, 1948-1949; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:6 (Box 7, Folder 6 [39153019710013])
    - Annual Report, 1949-1950; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:7 (Box 7, Folder 7 [39153019710021])
    - Annual Report, 1950-1951; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:8 (Box 7, Folder 8 [39153019710039])
      Annual Reports; Women in community organization; Advisory boards; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Annual Report, 1951-1952; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:9 (Box 7, Folder 9 [39153019710047])
    - Annual Report, 1952-1953; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:10 (Box 7, Folder 10 [39153019710054])
    - Annual Report, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:11 (Box 7, Folder 11 [39153019710062])
    - Annual Report, 1955; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:12 (Box 7, Folder 12 [39153019710070])
    - Annual Report, 1956; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:13 (Box 7, Folder 13 [39153019710088])
    - Annual Report, 1957; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:14 (Box 7, Folder 14 [39153019710096])
    - Annual Report, 1958; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:15 (Box 7, Folder 15 [39153019710104])
    - Annual Report, 1959; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:16 (Box 7, Folder 16 [39153019710112])
    - Annual Report, 1960; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:17 (Box 7, Folder 17 [39153019710120])
    - Annual Report, 1961; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box7:18 (Box 7, Folder 18 [39153019710138])
    - Annual Report, 1962; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:1 (Box-folder 8:1, Folder 1 [39153019710146])
      Women in community organization; Annual Reports; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Annual Report, 1963; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:2 (Box-folder 8:2, Folder 2 [39153019710153])
      Annual Reports; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Annual Report, 1964; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:3 (Box 8, Folder 3 [39153019710161])
    - Annual Report, 1965; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:4 (Box 8, Folder 4 [39153019710179])
    - Annual Reports, 1966; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:5 (Box 8, Folder 5 [39153019710187])
      Annual Reports
    - Annual Reports, 1967; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:6 (Box-folder 8:6)
    - Annual Reports, 1968; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:7 (Box-folder 8:7)
    - Annual Reports, 1969; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:8 (Box-folder 8:8)
    - Annual Reports, 1970; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:9 (Box-folder 8:9)
    - Annual Reports, 1971; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:10 (Box-folder 8:10)
    - Annual Reports, 1972; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:11 (Box-folder 8:11)
    - Annual Reports, 1973; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:12 (Box-folder 8:12)
    - Annual Report, 1974; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:13 (Box-folder 8:13)
    - Annual Reports, 1975; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:14 (Box-folder 8:14)
    - Annual Reports, Material for 1976 Report, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box8:15 (Box-folder 8:15)
  - Subseries B: Bureau History and Functions, 1940-1976
    - Bureau History - History and function of bureau, 1946-1974; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box8:16 (Box 8, Folder 16 [39153019710294])
      Women in community organization; Connecticut (state); Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Bureau History - Leaflets, 1961-1975; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box8:17 (Box-folder 8:17)
      Leaflets (printed works); Nonprofit organizations; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Bureau History - Procedural file, circa 1949; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box8:18 (Box 8, Folder 18 [39153019710310])
      Administrative records; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Bureau History - Advisory Board, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box8:19 (Box 8, Folder 19 [39153019710328])
      Administrative records; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Bureau History - Advisory Board, 1955; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box8:20 (Box 8, Folder 20 [39153019710336])
    - Bureau History - Advisory Board, 1966, 1969, 1976; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box8:21 (Box-folder 8:21)
      Advisory boards; Administrative records; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Bureau History: Advisory Board / Coordinating Committee, 1944; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:1 (Box-folder 9:1)
    - Bureau History - Advisory Board, Coordinating Committee, 1945; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:2 (Box 9, Folder 2 [39153019710427])
    - Bureau History - Advisory Board, Coordinating Committee, 1946-1947, 1949; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:3 (Box 9, Folder 3 [39153019710419])
    - Bureau History - Advisory Board, Sample Correspondence I, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:4 (Box 9, Folder 4 [39153019710401])
    - Bureau History - Advisory Board, Sample Correspondence II, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:5 (Box 9, Folder 5 [39153019710393])
      Correspondence; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Bureau History - Cooperating Committee, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:6 (Box 9, Folder 6 [39153019710385])
      Administrative records; Women in community organization; Advisory boards; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Bureau History - Cooperating Committee, 1955; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:7 (Box 9, Folder 7 [39153019710377])
    - Bureau History - Cooperating Committee, Subcommittees, 1955; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:8 (Box 9, Folder 8 [39153019710369])
    - Bureau History - Cooperating Committee, 1966; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:9 (Box 9, Folder 9 [39153019710609])
    - Bureau History - Cooperating Committee, 1971-1976; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:10 (Box 9, Folder 10 [39153019710591])
    - Bureau History - Cooperating Committee, Reports, 1976; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:11 (Box 9, Folder 11 [39153019710583])
      Administrative records; Reports; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Bureau History - Subcommittees, Community Listing, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:12 (Box 9, Folder 12 [39153019710575])
    - Bureau History - F. Harrison, 1973; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:13 (Box 9, Folder 13 [39153019710567])
    - Bureau History - B. Auerbach, Articles, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:14 (Box 9, Folder 14 [39153019710559])
      Administrative records; articles; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.; Auerbach, Beatrice Fox, 1887-1968
    - Bureau History - B. Auerbach, 1940-1949; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:15 (Box 9, Folder 15 [39153019710542])
      Administrative records; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.; Auerbach, Beatrice Fox, 1887-1968
    - Bureau History - B. Auerbach, 1950-1959; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:16 (Box 9, Folder 16 [39153019710534])
    - Bureau History - B. Auerbach, 1964-1968; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:17 (Box 9, Folder 17 [39153019710526])
    - Bureau History - B. Auerbach, Memorial articles, 1968 November 30 - December 3; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau History/Box9:18 (Box 9, Folder 18 [39153019710518])
      Administrative records; articles; Women in community organization; Advisory boards; Woodhouse, Chase Going.; Auerbach, Beatrice Fox, 1887-1968
    - Bureau History - C.G. Woodhouse, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service BureauBureau History/Box9:19 (Box 9, Folder 19 [39153019710500])
  - Subseries C: Correspondence, 1944-1980
    - Auerbach, B., 1944-1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Correspondence/Box9:20 (Box 9, Folder 20 [39153019710492])
    - Auerbach, B., 1956-1969; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Correspondence/Box9:21 (Box 9, Folder 21 [39153019710484])
    - Harrison, F., 1945-1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Correspondence/Box9:22 (Box 9, Folder 22 [39153019710476])
    - Woodhouse, C. G., 1952-1962; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Correspondence/Box9:23 (Box 9, Folder 25 [39153019710468])
    - Woodhouse, C. G., 1963-1980; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Correspondence/Box9:24 (Box 9, Folder 24 [39153019710450])
    - Other Service Bureau Representatives, 1950-1975; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Correspondence/Box9:25 (Box 9, Folder 25 [39153019710765])
      Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Administrative records; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Important Signatures, 1949-1973; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Correspondence/Box9:26 (Box 9, Folder 26 [39153019710757])
  - Subseries D: Bureau Activities, undated, 1945-1981
    - Calendars, 1945-1949; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau Activities/Box9:27 (Box-folder 9:27)
      Administrative records; Calendars; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
    - Calendars, 1950-1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau Activities/Box9:28 (Box 9, Folder 28 [39153019710732])
    - Calendars, 1955-1959; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau Activities/Box9:29 (Box 9, Folder 29 [39153019710724])
      Administrative records; Calendars; Advisory boards; Women in community organization
    - Calendars, 1960-1964; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau Activities/Box9:30 (Box 9, Folder 30 [39153019710716])
    - Calendars, 1965-1969; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau Activities/Box9:31 (Box 9, Folder 31 [39153019710708])
    - Calendars, 1970-1976; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Bureau Activities/Box9:32 (Box 9, Folder 32 [39153019710690])
    - Meetings
      - Annual Conferences, 1950-1951; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box9:33 (Box-folder 9:33)
      - Annual Conferences, Programs, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:1 (Box 10, Folder 1 [39153019710674])
      - Annual Conferences, Attendance, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:2 (Box 10, Folder 2 [39153019710666])
      - Annual Conferences,Foreign Guests, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:3 (Box 10, Folder 3 [39153019710658])
      - Annual Conferences, Foreign Aid Panel, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:4 (Box 10, Folder 4 [39153019710641])
      - Annual Conference, Correspondence, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:5 (Box 10, Folder 5 [39153019710633])
        Administrative records; Correspondence; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
      - Annual Conferences, Children's Book Exhibits, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:6 (Box 10, Folder 6 [39153019710625])
        Administrative records; Exhibitions; Advisory boards; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
      - Annual Conferences, Publicity and Logistics, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:7 (Box 10, Folder 7 [39153019710617])
      - Annual Conferences, 1955; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:8 (Box 10, Folder 8 [39153019710773])
      - Annual Conferences, 1956-1976; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:9 (Box 10, Folder 9 [39153019710781])
      - Annual Conferences, Conference Classes, 1962; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:10 (Box 10, Folder 10 [39153019710799])
      - Annual Conferences, Speakers, 1962; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:11 (Box 10, Folder 11 [39153019710807])
      - Annual Conferences, Foreign Guests, 1962; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:12 (Box 10, Folder 12 [39153019710815])
      - Annual Conferences, Planning and Logistics, 1962; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:13 (Box 10, Folder 13 [39153019710823])
      - Annual Conferences 1963, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:14 (Box 10, Folder 14 [39153019710831])
      - Annual Conferences 1969, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:15 (Box 10, Folder 15 [39153019710849])
      - Annual Conferences 1972, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:16 (Box 10, Folder 16 [39153019710856])
      - Annual Conferences 1975 Speakers Attendance, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:17 (Box 10, Folder 17 [39153019710864])
      - Annual Conferences 1975 Publicity, Overall Logistics, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:18 (Box-folder 10:18, Folder 18 [39153019710872])
      - Annual Conferences 1975 Eastern Region, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:19 (Box-folder 10:19)
      - Annual Conference 1975 Central Region, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:20 (Box 10, Folder 20 [39153019710898])
      - Annual Conferences 1975 Southwest Region, 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:21 (Box 10, Folder 21 [39153019710906])
      - Annual Conference Who's who, 1953-1955; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:22 (Box 10, Folder 22 [39153019710914])
      - Annual Conference Who's Who, 1956-1957; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:23 (Box 10, Folder 23 [39153019710922])
      - Annual Conferences Who's Who, 1958-1959; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:24 (Box 10, Folder 24 [39153019710930])
      - Annual Conferences Who's Who, 1960-1961; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:25 (Box 10, Folder 25 [39153019710948])
      - Attendance list, 1952-1955; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:26 (Box 10, Folder 26 [39153019710955])
      - Attendance Lists, 1956-1957; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:27 (Box-folder 10:27)
      - Attendance Lists, 1958-1959; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box10:28 (Box 10, Folder 28 [39153019710971])
      - Attendance Lists, 1960; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/BureauActivites/Meetings/Box11:1 (Box-folder 11:1)
        Meetings; Women in community organization; Administrative records; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
      - Attendance Lists, 1961-1962; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/BureauActivites/Meetings/Box11:2 (Box-folder 11:2)
        Administrative records; Meetings; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
      - Attendance Lists, 1963-1964; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/BureauActivites/Meetings/Box11:3 (Box-folder 11:3)
      - Attendance Lists, 1965-1967; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/BureauActivites/Meetings/Box11:4 (Box-folder 11:4)
      - Attendance Lists, 1968-1970; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/BureauActivities/Meetings/Box11:5 (Box-folder 11:5)
      - Attendance Lists, 1971-1972; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service BureauBureauActivites//Meetings/Box11:6 (Box-folder 11:6)
      - Attendance Lists, 1973-1976; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/BureauActivites/Meetings/Box11:7 (Box-folder 11:7)
      - Child Welfare, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/BureauActivities/Meetings/Box11:8 (Box-folder 11:8)
        Child welfare; Women in community organization; Administrative records; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
      - Community organization, undated; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Meetings/Box11:9 (Box-folder 11:9)
        Administrative records; Women in community organization
      - Conference series reports, 1947-1948; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:10 (Box 11, Folder 10 [39153019711649])
        Reports; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
      - Conference series reports, 1949; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:11 (Box 11, Folder 11 [39153019711656])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1950; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:12 (Box 11, Folder 12 [39153019711664])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1951; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:13 (Box 11, Folder 13 [39153019711672])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1952; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:14 (Box 11, Folder 14 [39153019711680])
        Reports; Women in community organization; Woodhouse, Chase Going.
      - Conference Series Reports, 1953; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:15 (Box 11, Folder 15 [39153019711698])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1954; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:16 (Box 11, Folder 16 [39153019711706])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1955; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:17 (Box 11, Folder 17 [39153019711714])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1956; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:18 (Box 11, Folder 18 [39153019711722])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1957; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:19 (Box 11, Folder 19 [39153019711730])
      - Conference Series Reports, 1958; 1983-0009/SeriesII:Auerbach Service Bureau/Annual Reports/Box11:20 (Box 11, Folder 20 [39153019711748])